venuebookingz.com 2016-05-15

# Privacy policy of Venuebookingz

venuebookingz™ respects your right to privacy and we are committed to protecting it. Accordingly, we abide by the following principles and policies for all of the Personally Identifiable Information we collect from you and we are committed to following them in our day-to-day operations. This Privacy Policy details certain policies implemented throughout venuebookingz's Site and Services governing venuebookingz™'s use of Personally Identifiable Information submitted by users. 

As our business grows and changes, we expect to revise or enhance these policies from time-to-time. We will post a current version of our Privacy Policy on our Site and will communicate material changes to our Privacy Policy to users and the public by posting a notice on our Site for ten days following the change. If any modification is unacceptable to you, you shall cease using our Site and Services. If you do not cease using our Site and Services, you will be conclusively deemed to have accepted the change. 

## Correcting/Updating Personally Identifiable Information

venuebookingz™ provides you with the ability to review, correct and delete any of the Personally Identifiable Information that you have provided to us at any time. If you have questions about this Privacy Policy or wish to review or correct any information you have provided to us, you may do so by (i) accessing your account online, (ii) submitting an email request to us at: 

venuebookingz@gmail.com, Attn: venuebookingz™ Privacy Policy 

## What Information We Collect

We only collect Personally Identifiable Information about you from our Site if you choose to provide it to us. This means you can visit our Site without revealing any Personally Identifiable Information. Like most web sites, our web servers do collect information about your visit, but not about you personally. This information may include the URL, IP address, browser type and language, and the date and time of your visit. 

In order to use certain features of the Site and Services you may be asked to register. Any Personally Identifiable Information which is required and that you choose to provide within the registration process will not be disclosed on our Site. Once registered, you may provide additional information in various areas of the site. Providing additional information beyond the fields in the registration process is entirely optional and such information may be visible to the public. 

##  How We Use the Personally Identifiable Information You Provide To Us 

We may use your Personally Identifiable Information to register you to use our Services, to verify your authority to use certain features of our Site and Services, to improve and tailor the content and general administration of our Site and Services, and, based upon the email settings which you may select, to deliver certain content, information, services and notices from venuebookingz™ as well as communications regarding information, events, content, products and services of our third party partners. 

##  Opting In and Out of Email Communications from venuebookingz™ and Third Parties 

By providing your email address while signing up for venuebookingz™ or submitting a Demand via venuebookingz™'s Demand it! service you automatically grant permission to venuebookingz™ and its strategic alliance partners to send email communications to you. During the sign up and Demand it! process you may also indicate via a check-box whether you grant permission for venuebookingz™ to share your email address with additional third parties and for those third parties to send emails directly to you. You may manage your opt in preferences and opt out of receiving email communications by clicking "unsubscribe" from an email sent to you by venuebookingz™ or by signing in to venuebookingz™ online and managing your preferences. 

##  Disclosing Your Personally Identifiable Information to Others 

Except as expressly provided in this Privacy Policy, we do not disclose or market Personally Identifiable Information obtained through our Site to others. Based upon your opt in settings which you may manage as described above, we may from time to time provide your Personally Identifiable Information to third party partners for various purposes, including to allow those third party partners to contact you about news, events, products and/or services in which you may be interested. If you do not wish to be included on the list of users disclosed to our third party partners, you may indicate this preference during the sign up or Demand submission or you may manage your opt in preferences as described above. To stop receiving communications from a third party to whom we have already provided your information prior to your opting out, contact that third party directly or click unsubscribe from an email which you receive from the third party. We may disclose your personally identifiable information: (a) to complete a transaction that you initiate, (b) as required by law, (c) when necessary to protect the safety of customers, employees, or property, (d) when you specifically authorize it or (e) when required to service the company's system infrastructure. 

## Cookies, Web Beacons, and Other Internet Data

Like most web sites, we may use cookies, web log files, IP addresses, or web beacons in order to recognize you as a registered user, improve overall Site experience, tailor and customize the content of our Site, or track Site usage. This data may be exchanged between the user's computer, our Site, and the systems of our infrastructure partners. The linkage between this data and your Personally Identifiable Information is never shared without your permission or except when required by law. 

## Security and Data Storage

We employ procedural and technological security measures that are designed to safeguard your Personally Identifiable Information from loss, unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration or destruction. venuebookingz™ may use encryption, password protection, and other security measures to help prevent unauthorized access to your Personally Identifiable Information. 

## International Users

Our computer systems are currently based in the United States where data protection requirements and privacy regulations may be different than other parts of the world. If you create an online account on this website as a visitor from outside the United States, you will have agreed to the terms of this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use, you will have consented to processing of all such information in the United States, and you will have agreed that your personal information will be subject to the requirements of the privacy regulations of the United States, which may not offer an equivalent level of protection as certain other countries. 

## Children's Privacy

venuebookingz™ recognizes the privacy interests of children and we encourage parents and guardians to take an active role in their children's online activities. venuebookingz™'s Site and Services are not intended for children under the age of 13. venuebookingz™ does not target its Site and Services to children under 13. venuebookingz™ does not knowingly collect Personally Identifiable Information from children under the age of 13. 

## Assignment

You maintain ownership rights to your Personally Identifiable Information, even if there is a business transition. However, we may transfer your Personally Identifiable Information to a successor entity upon a merger, consolidation, or other corporate reorganization in which venuebookingz™ participates or to a purchaser of all or substantially all of venuebookingz™'s assets to which this Site relates. 

## Links to Third Party Sites

This privacy policy applies only to the privacy of users of venuebookingz™'s Site and Services. By using venuebookingz™'s Site and Services you agree to the terms of this privacy policy. If you move from venuebookingz™'s Site to external web sites owned or operated by other entities or individuals, you should check the privacy policies of those external web sites carefully. The terms by which the owners or operators of those external web sites manage your Personally Identifiable Information obtained at such third party sites could differ from how venuebookingz™ manages your Personally Identifiable Information. 

## Definitions

  * "Personally Identifiable Information" may include your name, address, telephone number, email address, or other information which by its nature can identify you personally. However, "Personally Identifiable Information" excludes any information that you choose to make available on parts of the Site that are accessible to the public such as your public profile and other publicly visible content that you may add to the Site. 
  * "venuebookingz™" refers to Venuebookingz™ Division, TIS Pvt. Ltd., a company. "venuebookingz™" and the venuebookingz™ logo are trademarks of venuebookingz™, venuebookingz.com are trademarks of venuebookingz™. 
  * "Site and Services" refer to the features and functionality ("Services") made available to users at the Internet web site located at the URL [venuebookingz.com](http://venuebookingz.com/) ("Site") and via email communications, mobile applications. 
.
